[
  {
    "question": "What does one create objects with?",
    "answer": "Constructors"
  },
  {
    "question": "What adjective do you use to describe something owned by a class instead of an object?",
    "answer": "Static"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is another name for superclasses of a class?",
    "answer": "Parents"
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you call functions associated with a class?",
    "answer": "Methods"
  },
  {
    "question": "What happens when a superclass and a subclass share an attribute with the same name?",
    "answer": "Shadowing"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the templates for design class structure called?",
    "answer": "Patterns"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you call the items a function is given when called?",
    "answer": "Arguments"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the A from ACID stand for (in the Computer Science context)",
    "answer": "Atomicity"
  },
  {
    "question": "Could you give me a synonym for a lazy list?",
    "answer": "Stream"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you call an object which doesn't change its internal state once constructed?",
    "answer": "Immutable"
  }
//this is just to fill them out easily, TODO remove this
,

  {
    "question": "",
    "answer": ""
  }

]